Mhm.
>> Mhm.
>> Ah, can you guys hear me? Hello, hello.
Hello everyone.
Ohayo gozaimasu. Good morning to all.
It's literally 2:00 a.m. and I slept
off. It's 1 hour since the
release day release of Watch Dogs.
And it's the game is out. I just woke
up.
>> [laughter]
>> I
had a GPU update and yeah, we're ready
to roll in.
And everything.
I got
a of snacks
All
set up. I slept for like what? 10:30 to
2:00 a.m. So, wait. 1 2 3
3 and 1/2 hours.
But, I have school today and work today.
So, we going to play Wild Dogs from two
from now right now till you count it as
2:30 a.m. onwards. So, 3:30 4:30 5:30
6:30. 4 hours, okay? 4 hours maximum,
okay?
Then, I got to uh freshen up uh freshen
up, get ready for work and everything.
[music] And then, we come back home.
Lock in.
>> [laughter]
>> We going to lock in.
We going to lock in. We going to lock in
and uh we going to play.
So, yeah. Let me switch to the game.
Give me a minute.
Squish you my I'm a take a sigh. As you
can see, the game is here.
Finally.
Game is here. Present enable 10. Logging
in. Let's go.
>> [laughter]
>> No, the [\h__\h] What the [\h__\h]
We got put in queue. What the [\h__\h]
No way.
I forgot.
I genuinely forgot.
No, don't do this to me.
Bro.
I forgot. I could have just woken up and
do it put be myself in the queue for it,
so I can like stream. [\h__\h] why did I
start the freaking stream now? Man.
No.
[\h__\h]
Oh my god.
None the key sweet tonight,
no.
How could I forget?
I've stayed up
waited for other game releases like
Wuthering Waves etc. other games, right?
How come I didn't even know?
No way this thing is happening with me.
Okay,
times like this
the best place to go is
Twitter.
Return.
No shield.
Return Twitter Twitter.
>> [clears throat]
>> Uh
>> Once I end, let me see if I can find
Also, uh for those who are new here, uh
also while we are raining, let me talk
about something.
They finally
They finally have some monetization
enabled on kick. kick.com/chocolax
Um
I've been waiting forever for kick
to have to be an
you know
Of course I could have done other means,
you know, but
I wanted to wait till a kick supported
the monetization for India cuz
for the longest time kick didn't have
that feature.
As in, the country was not available in
the onboarding thingy.
And finally it is. I'm so happy.
I'm really really happy. It's finally
possible that I have monetization
enabled enabled so you can um
you can send me gifts. You can send me
not not gifts.
Yeah, gifts. They call it kicks. You can
send me kicks on kick and also
subscriptions are and they are also
available.
Hm.
So what?
Now what goes on?
Wait, how much is kicks?
How much is it for one kick?
Oh, 500 kicks is like $5.29,
hey, but
It's like Twitch bits.
>> I'm sorry, folks. I should have I should
have double-checked.
I should have double-checked
before starting the stream.
What else should you comment?
I do kind of kind of want to like take a
shower and freshen up till it's
back back.
What should I do? I I stupidly started
my stream.
I I don't want to
Either I can keep on talking
until this this is available or
The thing is not I slept off.
I launched the game. There was a Windows
update, restarted.
No, there was GP update and I restarted.
Okay, all of those things are done.
I wanted to sleep early today like at
6:00 p.m. after coming back from classes
and stuff, but I got I had to do some
work.
Um
I I finally figured out figured out
figured out a way to automatically or
like use API to start and stop the
stream from Multimelt. That was like
making like a um command or like a
button in Sammy so I can use it for the
24/7 channel stuff. Cuz the only one
thing I've been having issues with um
with the 24 x 7 channel as it's working
great, perfect, everything is good, but
just that
uh the Twitch not to stream
automatically dies every 48 hours cuz
that's the maximum broadcasting limit
for the platform Twitch.
So,
yeah, I made it so that it can detect
your Twitch stream. If it detects that
the two streams is
or like stopped, it will automatically
start again. I made that thingy so I was
like trying my best to be patient enough
to
um what do you call it?
You remote control the cloud server.
Connect to the cloud server desktop and
like it's so laggy, man. You need like
tons of patience in order to like
um how do you say? In order to like do
it?
It's so pain.
I wonder if they'll enable like the what
do you call it?
Um I wonder if they're enable
like um I wonder if they'll enable like
firing range like last time the game.
Mhm, gold drops one. So, there's Twitch
drops happening.
So, there is Twitch drops happening,
which is great.
Uh
There is Twitch drops.
>> I'm going to lie.
Longest day. Yeah, hello Kalista.
Konbawa. Hello, hello.
I know what Konbawa is. Good.
Good morning, though.
Wait, access the what? Access denied?
Riot, give me access.
It's just increasing me in the queue.
I'm stuck in the queue.
>> [laughter]
>> Why? Why?
>> Should I just end stream?
Uh
No.
Pain.
Uh
Pain. Uh huh huh.
Uh huh.
Just like 200
\ 000
players playing right now this game.
Crazy, man.
That is
That is crazy.
Holy.
And how do I see the game stats? Global
player player game play stats.
The floodgates are still closed. Yeah,
why don't we do something else in the
meantime? Leave this and I
Yeah.
Let's Let's That's a good idea. Yeah. I
should have checked. I could have slept
for a bit.
I only slept for 3 or 4 hours.
From 10:30 to 2:00. I I was supposed to
stream at like 1 hour early, like 1:00
a.m.
When the flood gate When the floodgates
were open.
Um
Uh
Who
Pain
They do
Imagine Imagine Imagine Imagine
What if
It's What if we are still here for 3
hours and still It's still closed. 1:00
a.m. in the Hong Kong time? Yeah, it's
1:00 a.m. Yep, it's currently 2:32
a.m.
Yeah, I only had like a few bits of
sleep.
Um
and I have work and classes today. It's
a working day on Friday.
Yeah, I could have done this if this was
like Saturday
early morning and stuff like what we did
last time.
Last Saturday, same situation, right?
I think uh I was
up early and uh or Sunday or something,
I suppose. I was up early and waiting
for the
Watch Dogs thingy.
Mhm.
Yeah.
If I knew this, I could have taken a
little leave from work or something,
made an excuse like I'm feeling sick.
Can I come in on Monday
or something?
But no, uh but no no, this week no. My
second part-time job, I made a mistake.
Um I I'm I'm I'm my I recently started
my second part-time job, so my shift uh
I have to like register my shifts in the
in the app in an app.
So uh I didn't know how to use the app,
so I apparently it was not linked to the
company.
So
uh whatever I sent last week was not No,
last week I sent when I started I
Yeah, I think I sent on Monday
for this week and it that did not get
uh like approved like
um
that did not get received by the
company, so I had to re- go through the
linking process of the app again with
them.
And finally, it's linked. So, this week,
since I did not send it early before
Wednesday, shift like what days do I
want to work, what are my hours, what
like how many hours can I work in this
and that day,
like that.
So,
uh since I couldn't send it in time this
week um work I don't have work for the
second part-time job, but I'm uh
hall master or something on a restaurant
Japanese restaurant, so I have to like
serve
Uh yeah, I'm serving
the dishes and everything.
I have to read out the difficult kanji
name uh difficult Japanese names of the
of these these delicious Japanese
Christine
stuff, but yeah.
Uh uh
so, yeah, next week onwards I don't
think I can do this like Fridays and
stuff. I'll be coming home really late.
Like uh 10:00 a.m. 10:00 p.m. 11:00 p.m.
Work ends by 9:00 and sometimes 10:00.
Um
hanging on that.
So, I have to come back home get on the
train, get back home eat something and
hop on stream if possible, if I'm not
too tired
on Fridays. Saturdays and Sundays I'm
always going to take a leave, so I can
stream.
Why you have eight dogs? Cuz wild dogs.
But we are in a queue, we have to
Wait, wait, wait. It says 73,000. Wait.
Wait, wait, they're letting the people
in.
Oh my god, they're letting people in.
I know No, I have 80 but not not 80%.
20% of the people are worldwide people
are in already, but
but um
yeah, they're finally letting people
It's 73 now. Oh my god.
Let's go.
All right.
Also, I You know guys, I asked my
um
So, for those who don't know, I have a
QQ group. It's like a Discord server.
Not Discord server, it's like a WhatsApp
group or something for China.
Those who use QQ.
So, I asked like if anyone is willing
wanting to play this game with me.
Because um
Because like how do you say it?
As you know, last last two streams I
played Watch Dogs during the closed beta
like beta.
Right?
Um
closed beta
Um there are Chinese people, right? From
mainland China and stuff. So, I was like
wondering, yeah.
If they can play with me now, that would
be so nice. We'll have that
connectivity.
Cuz we barely
uh like play and do stuff together cuz
I'm not streaming on Bilibili.
And you need like 1,000 followers on
Bilibili to stream. It's really
pain.
So, yeah.
Sorry, Remina. I couldn't hear if you
replied. Yeah, it's because of Watch
Dogs.
Uh it's the release date for the game. I
have pre-ordered the game. I have the
game.
Uh I technically bought the game, so I'm
uh wanting to replay the game
on its release date today.
Right now, it's going to be getting
released now. If I was in India now, it
this wouldn't be a problem. It's like
9:30 p.m. when the release happen like
the when the global launch happens.
So, I can just easily play till 2:00 or
1:00 a.m. Indian time and then go sleep,
right? But here, it's already midnight.
It's 2:00 2:38 a.m. right now, but yeah.
I have work.
It's 11:00 p.m. here. Ah.
Yeah, it's going to be 11:00 now.
Um
What do you call it? Um Oh, yeah, it's
11:00.
It's 2:30 now, so it's 11:00. Yeah,
yeah, yeah.
Um what do you call it?
Um I have work today, classes and
everything. It's a
working day today for me.
So, I can only play up to
uh
7,000. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god.
Oh my god. They're going to let me in
soon. Oh my god. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go.
Oh my god. Let's go. Let's go. Oh my
god. Oh my god. Oh my god.
Uh let's go.
Yeah.
Okay. Um ba ba ba ba ba. Uh I What was I
doing? I forgot. Um
Uh
Mm.
Okay. They
They restarted the queue. That's why
every They're letting people more people
in. Okay, got it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. They're
getting a little They're
[\h__\h] you.
Oh my god. I'm sorry for cursing. Bro.
Bro.
>> [laughter]
>> Bro.
Oh, wait. I forgot. I forgot. It's Oh,
[\h__\h] I forgot. It's
2:00 a.m. I shouldn't be screaming right
now. [\h__\h] I'm I'm not at home. I'm not
in India in my own house. I'm in a Japan
I'm in Japan. I have a roommates. I
mean,
neighbors. And so, my roommate is went
to work. He has a night shift. So,
Wednesday, Thursday, Friday No.
Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, he goes for
work, so I can like um
do late night streams if I want.
Um
I mean, I can always do
as long as I have enough sleep and I can
wake up in time and everything.
Oh,
man. Why?
Cali's on. Why?
Why?
>> [laughter]
>> Why did you call them and be like Yeah,
close the gates again.
You got to
You got to let more people in, but they
got to wait more again.
Back in the line.
>> [laughter]
>> Um
But, yeah, I'm so excited for this game,
man.
Yeah, I have to connect my account,
right? For
Go to bed, Jaxa.
What is that thing? Nah.
Nice choice to do the stream. Nah. I
bought You know I am broke broke
broke
and I bought so much stuff just for this
one stream. I mean, today and tomorrow.
Yeah. Have
Um
And the day after tomorrow, Sunday, too.
Like for
Yeah.
And like there's so much I have to say.
Like I bought stuff
even though I was broke.
And I don't know what to do, but yeah.
Like
one of the not
I I actually got
It's not scolded. It's more like a
reality check.
Am I Am I
What do you call it?
Uh
Recently now, I get we can talk talk
while the game is
doing its thing.
Yeah, so recently now
I've been in this dilemma or this
thought process like, "Huh,
what should I do?"
Like as you know, like when I play games
or when I do my streams lately,
uh I'm I can only give out
3,000 bitrate, so that looks really
awful
when you are watching,
right? When you're watching the stream,
it looks really bad or something because
it's so blurry and stuff, right? The
gameplay and everything.
So, uh I for today's stream, I'm locally
recording it.
God knows how big Oh god, Juggernaut
says ended us that you
What?
Kick stream? What? What happened to
Kick?
What happened to Kick?
What? What happened to Kick?
Never mind. Uh Oh, wait. Don't give me
false.
Oh my god, this program
It stop It stop making me Oh my god.
Yeah, so I
I'm starting to locally record, so
then War Dogs is also doing that. Also,
is that what I see it is? Logging in?
Okay, they're getting me getting me in
the game.
Oh, yeah. Let's go.
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] I'm screaming I'm screaming
the [\h__\h]
I screamed I screamed.
[\h__\h] I screamed I screamed.
Okay okay okay.
Oh my god guys the game is here the game
is here.
Oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god.
Oh my god let's go let's go.
Wait a minute where is the AK-47 hello.
Hello what? Okay okay okay okay hi hi hi
hi.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay what the [\h__\h] why did I choose
tutorial stupid oh my god.
Ah.
I'm so hyped I'm so hyped.
Oh my god oh my.
And it's so cold here you know how much
degree Celsius it is it's 19 degree
Celsius it's cold cold.
Oh my god.
>> [clears throat]
>> Oh wait I forgot to connect my. Oh.
Twitch so I don't I can't get drops.
Oh drop next.
Kick.
That's chocolate.
All right.
You know I have so much so much ideas
planned out for this game now I'm going
to I'm going to I'm going to stream this
game. Um a lot.
I don't know why it's my first time on a
milsim type of games but
I feel like
I mean, it's long hype, okay?
I had the same thing going on with Arc
Raiders.
I know I bought the game after like a
month three months three months.
I jumped in. Oh, I I know
Oh, wait.
No, no. Don't don't go
don't go teasing me.
I know how to play the game.
Boom.
I I'll watch you I'll watch me be pro at
the game.
I can assure you that.
Can I get some hot water?
My throat is
going burr.
Is it just me or am I supposed to wait
this whole time just for a tutorial?
Okay. Thank you.
Bakurani
Okay. I'm an infant.
It'll be nice if
if nothing else I can sell off a nurse
on Twitch.
Wait, you actually phoned me from Arc
Raiders?
Wait.
Huh?
Wait, really?
Wait. it. Wait, really really really?
Wait, what?
Hold on. No way. No, I for real thought
you found me through found me
from Valorant Smith or something.
One second, let me look this up.
Yeah.
What the
So So I I I assumed I was wrong. You
know?
Uh
yeah, it's it should be.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's Yeah, Valorant
Smith. Valorant Smith.
I remember you well because you asked me
so much questions that time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> [clears throat]
>> Valorant Smith. Uh I wonder how that
game is doing. It's been a while.
Yeah, it was Valorant.
Maybe I'm remembering that wrong. Hmm.
Valorant.
Wait, was it Valorant? Wait, it is
Shokun. You You found me from
YouTube first, right? Or did you come
like
No, wait.
Oh, yeah, it was Twitch for you as well.
Not at all.
Let me check my Discord.
Let's check.
Uh
And it's June 19th. Wait, where did you
come from? Did you initially came from
>> [snorts]
>> YouTube or Twitch? Twitch, Shokun.
Uh then
Oh, yeah. You uh yeah, yeah, I remember.
Uh you were
uh You You followed me through Jasmine.
To Jasmine's uh yeah, yeah. We were
playing We were playing uh Metamorphan.
Uh I forgot.
Enter the realm house, yeah.
But I have to do this.
Uh is this potato graphics, actually?
Did they actually give me the option?
Performance quality.
No.
No, they don't They can't give me potato
graphics for shadows. [\h__\h]
No.
No. Just cuz I have a good PC. I don't
have a good PC. I'm sure I'm I'm on a
single setup. Single PC setup. I I
It's uh [\h__\h] Okay, it's fine.
Projector.
Game is stuck.
All right.
>> Yeah.
Yeah.
Thank you, John War Dog.
I think that's his name, John War Dog,
right? I think.
Uh next room, where this way?
Hello.
How's the stream quality?
Uh what? Okay.
Okay.
It's hard to see with the potato
graphics.
Okay.
Rip.
What do you mean, rip?
What happened? What happened?
Okay.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay.
Get me out. Get me out. Get me out. I
want to get into Battlefield.
Yeah, we're doing the re
hand rub hand rubbing.
We're doing hand rubbing.
Cuz we're rubbing him.
That's why it's taking so long. I'm
doing magic to revive him.
>> [groaning]
[screaming]
>> And you died.
>> Or you could just use your hands to
revive him again. Using proper medical
equipment makes the process way faster.
Grab a resuscitator from the vendor's
item selection and see for yourself.
>> Resuscitator.
>> Now, drag that guy away from the danger
before resuscitating him.
>> You're going going into my
basement.
I mean, my container.
Hoi.
Let's go.
>> Stand in that large white circle on THE
FLOOR.
THIS IS THE CONTROL ZONE.
EVERY faction competes
>> Okay.
>> to hold this zone.
The faction with the most players in the
zone when the score timer ticks over
earns a point. The first team to reach
100 points wins the match.
Stay in the control zone.
Know that your presence here is
contributing to your team's score in the
bottom left of your screen and that
you're earning money for doing so in the
top right.
>> Mhm.
When does work start?
Uh I have to leave by I have work starts
at 9:00. I have to leave by 8:30.
8:30 before 8:30, no matter what. So,
I'm thinking of wrapping the stream up
by like 6:30
or 7:00.
30.
Yeah, 7:30's good. I can take a bath and
like yeah.
Let me make that Instagram story.
[\h__\h]
Not going to sleep. I slept for 3 hours.
I want to sleep, but I can't.
It's fine.
I got
items Let's take care.
That's some That's painkillers.
Oh, yeah. Building.
All right.
items
It's like Fortnite. Like hitting the
weak points.
>> To bring out your instructors, you need
to be in the city with a forward
operating
fob.
Go and get your fob from the vendor.
Place the fob where you can
by pressing and holding left click.
Open the fob and drag the hammer into
your special item slot, slot three.
This slot is reserved for specialist
role items.
>> Okay.
>> Medical bags and RPGs.
>> Uh, okay.
>> Now you have the hammer equipped, right
click to bring up the build
>> Bonk, bonk, bonk, bonk.
>> Escalators.
AH,
>> [groaning]
>> THAT'S GOOD.
THAT CONCLUDES YOUR TRAINING.
FEEL FREE TO LEAVE THE compound and
check out the shooting AND VEHICLE
RANGES.
>> IT'S OVER.
Completed tutorial.
Let's go.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Uh.
Ha ha ha ha.
Wait, I have enhanced broadcasting on.
How?
I have to learn how to do the enhanced
broadcasting stuff for my war channel.
My 24 x 7 channel cuz I don't want it to
be sending any of the video.
I mean, it's a cloud server, so it's
fine. It can handle it.
But generally though,
too much.
Okay, settings. We got to do some stuff
with the settings.
Controls.
Um should be looking at
air.
Yeah, this one. Yaw and pitch.
Yeah, I want to train my
helicopter skills before I get into the
match.
>> Look what the cat dragged in.
>> Okay.
I'm going to learn the helicopter first.
Cuz I'm going to be a pilot.
I'm going to go sleep, jog, hello, work,
I have to go to work early tomorrow.
Number 10, good luck, good luck, good
luck.
Thanks for coming by dropping by now.
Daijobu, daijobu. Sleep well.
>> I don't want that. Seems nice.
Good night. I love with the game. Hi.
I crashed. [\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> Uh okay.
I crashed.
Am I actually far away?
I am.
Anyway, let's go back to the game.
Mhm.
We'll learn as we go.
Jinxed. Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> Uh the play server browser. Let's go.
They have filters now. Show community.
Classic King of the experience all the
car
enable hardcore standard with minimal UI
no dynamic Australia hard cook animals
good slots minimal health bar
or inventory mode at all attack vehicle
constant and stuff disable no thanks
mini guns little words you may have
knees zombies defense
vehicle okay okay
Uh max cash.
Oh, we can get in the get on Asia
server.
Number one, let's go.
>> Failed to connect on a reasonable time.
Hello there.
And so welcome. Good morning.
Come on, get me in.
Uh why is it taking so forever to join?
Huh?
Max current players should be
95.
Is that Is that Stefanonia?
Wait, where is the new map?
What's the new map called?
Also, it's not letting me join a server.
Weird.
Are they queuing for the game? Yeah, we
were waiting for queue and
they're letting people in. They They
reset at the queue
and now they're letting people in.
Yeah, now they're letting people in.
Uh
da da da
Come on.
Failed to join. Server is full. Tonight
only.
If it's full, why is it not showing that
it's full?
Ah.
Black market
$200
No, you stupid ah.
I accidentally bought five five
bandages. [\h__\h]
I forgot it uses game money.
No.
Ah, [sighs]
bakabaka you baka.
Middle finger.
I needed I need this.
Player skills load outs
I kept skins.
Black and gold
Um
SK from Tarkov
Is it it's kind of similar but not
really.
I feel like
And not really the way
Stay in queue.
Well, let me check the Twitter. So, it's
basically like Battlefield but not
really Battlefield.
You You can do other task rather than
shooting.
Your main goal is to make money. So,
yeah.
There is that.
Uh
Why is it not letting me
Region Asia East.
Should I join Oceania server or
something?
I don't know.
Unable to connect your game server is
offline.
Or you may be not connected to the What
the hell? Am I live?
First of all.
Oh, come on.
Okay. Uh is it showing anything?
Hey. not supposed to select a multiple.
Or you can even the this is a bug.
Okay.
And if it's a bug, can I join?
Can I join this?
The word Q is full. Why every server is
full? Oh, yeah. Of course, it's a launch
day, but still.
Okay, let's go with Asia Southeast.
What the
I can't get into any servers.
I thought they did
extinct.
Are you able to see the number of people
in No, I can't.
Are you talking about the main
screen stuff?
Oh, I went past that now. They let me
in.
But I can't see the number of people
queued up for the server browser.
Over here, I cannot see that.
Wait, are you also playing
the game? Did you buy the game?
I need to restart it. If I restart, I'll
be in back in queue.
Cuz there's so many people trying to get
in.
I do want to restart.
What if I go to America or something?
I can only choose max three servers. Uh
I'll choose all of Asia.
How do you see the queue? It's like
Yeah, changing region might work, yeah.
Good way.
East
next to a rest.
Nope, nothing happens.
And now I I think I'll I'll quit the
game and restart, I guess.
Yeah.
I get
That's fine. It's fine. It's fine.
Um
Give me a minute.
Think it's closed, yeah.
Uh
Before doing that, I need to connect to
my
Twitch drops now.
Let me just do that real quick.
Oh, there's Arc Traders drops as well,
but yeah.
Uh War Dogs www
They should
uh put put it in alphabetical order for
these stuff now, like
um
Oh, wait, it's
It's based on
um
date now.
Why dogs uh
connected
Okay, I have to log in to the game. No,
what Yeah, log in to the wild dog.
Yeah, let me
sign in.
Oh, yeah. Link my Twitch account. Yes,
authorize.
And imagine if they allow just like
Twitch now, if they allow YouTube drops
now, that's going to be so crazy.
But YouTube won't do it.
Sucks.
Uh
Now, literally stuck Many people are
stuck at the server browser thing. It
none of them are able to join.
Uh
>> Even North America doesn't work.
Huh?
Um
Okay, I'm launching the game, by the
way.
Server queue is full.
>> [clears throat]
>> My gun from six
I was checking this on other streamer on
Twitch.
Uh
I want to join this streamer's blood dog
recruitment thingy
as part of Japan team or something.
But the thing is now I have school today
and work today, so I cannot stay
and
participate
uh in their thingy
and play together with them. It'll be a
good opportunity to play with the big
streamer, but
yeah.
Uh
Hm.
>> Must be a follower or speak.
Oh, game is here. Don't tell me it's
going to send me to queue.
Of course they they're going to send me
to queue.
Now we wait.
Wait.
Oh, cool.
Uh
game optimizer.
I I saw on Twitter about Kojima getting
Kojima Productions getting dropped by
for their game percent. Like Sony's not
taking it and
>> [laughter]
>> uh
crazy.
Wait, Microsoft Japan and Sony are like
on like nearby. What?
>> [laughter]
>> What?
I didn't know that.
Damn, Tokyo.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh my god, I just saw this on Twitter.
Like that was crawling for Watch Dogs.
Bro.
Okay, wait. What did it say? Oh, I mean
I'm in. Guys, we are in.
Watch Dogs security initializing. Okay.
Nah, it's still bugged.
>> [clears throat]
>> I made it to work in to anyone on our
effects.
I don't know if I'm I've broken the
servers, I fear.
I don't know if I'm
I'm
Bro, everyone is getting timed out. Come
on.
If you're stuck in queue to even join
WildWorks, don't stress. Our version
isn't working. When it does,
95% of the servers are capacity.
Uh
the rest won't load.
Ah, so everyone is getting timed out.
Is it something like No, no, no, no, no,
no. Not my internet. It's the actual
game servers.
It's maxed out now.
A lot of people are having this issue.
Bro.
Uh ta-ta.
Uh
Mhm.
I really wish I could like play some
good music rather than this music, but
I'm streaming on YouTube now, so I can't
play like
copyrighted music.
Mhm.
Well, that sucks. No.
They were not ready of Yeah, I guess
they were not ready.
I'll do one thing.
Mhm.
I have 3 hours to pass, right?
Let's do one thing.
I'll get something to eat.
Uh
I wonder what other people are doing
right now.
Like on Twitch.
Let's see.
Are everyone playing Everyone is
playing, what the hell?
Ena is playing.
Oh, yeah, so many people are stuck at
the
server browser. Some people are playing.
Many are stuck at the server browser.
Some people are playing.
So many people are at the server
browser.
At this point, I can just play hop on
firing range and just play firing range.
That's better, I guess.
Yeah, that's better, I guess.
Any update from them?
No time.
Okay, I'll just play in the firing range
and shoot at
dummies.
They should add bot bots or something.
Like a
like an actual test
of how it is
in the battlefield rather than real
people. Something.
If I knew this was happening, I could
have just not done the launch day
stream.
I could have just
actually simply just
um
waited till everything has calmed down.
>> Oh, come on then. So much for [\h__\h]
down time.
>> Oh my god, everything is laggy.
Why is it laggy?
>> [clears throat and cough]
>> Let me close my browser.
Is that a
flying sound? Oh, damn.
Okay, wait.
Uh, hashtag wire dogs.
>> [clears throat]
>> So many people are review bombing the
game because they are like stuck at the
waiting queue and can't play the game
and stuff.
Where
How much does fly my helicopter?
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] No one saw that.
No one saw that.
Okay, never mind. Again.
That was bad.
>> I'm going to try something new.
Spend money to make money.
>> Okay.
Let's go.
Uh
Why don't I have control?
I think the mouse left and right
is the yaw, but up and down is messing
it up
a little bit.
Yeah, it is messing it up a little bit.
>> I'm only using my mouse right now.
Uh the game is kind of laggy.
Wait, how did I survive that?
What the hell?
How did I survive that?
You guys also saw that, right? Oh my
god, I survived that.
Let me go back to base.
My game is glitchy. What is this?
What is this?
Oh my gosh.
Now I cannot
get
altitude.
Oh my god, I almost did not crash.
No.
Okay, now it's fixed.
Okay.
Bro, what is going on?
Did you see that?
What just happened?
Oh, what just happened?
That's crazy.
>> I'm back swinging.
Oh god, no.
Okay, how do I do a jet run?
I go like this.
Now, I'm going backwards when I do that.
>> Okay.
We go We go again for our
flight activities.
I'm literally playing how to fly.
I'm literally learning how to fly the
game. Fly the airplane.
Okay.
Let the wind guide me.
Oh, no.
The map is so big, though.
I finished playing.
What is this base?
Uh-oh.
How did I crash land?
I was
How did I
Um
Thanks.
Oh, wait. So, I was I back?
Wait, so was I back?
Wait.
Um
>> Oh.
North America
>> Uh
It's not.
Mhm.
Okay, we're back to
Let's go back to our airplane stuff. I
mean, helicopter stuff.
That is pain.
Mhm.
Wait, Doom is free?
Doom 1 and 2? Oh, I already received I
already claimed that. Oh.
Pain.
Mhm.
Amazon Luna
There's more games now.
Botany Manor
and some mini games
Yeah, I got them.
Rather than going to vendors, they
should give us a way to
I
They should give us a way to like
access
What do you call it?
access like
weapons and stuff from the menu itself
rather than going to vendors.
Mhm.
I want to unlock the
bow.
medical pack
>> Now you're speaking my language.
>> Oh my god, they have a bow in this game.
That's the reason why I wanted to
play the game cuz they have a
freaking bow, man. They have a bow, man.
I love games which has bow, man.
That's the best feeling ever.
>> What are you looking for?
Come back anytime.
>> Okay, we're going in.
Okay.
>> I think a helicopter should be flying
way more altitude.
Okay, that's the wrong key. How to do a
J-turn?
[\h__\h]
Mhm, mhm, I'm getting
Ah, it's crashing. It's lagging.
I'm getting it on the
What? Um
40 FPS in game.
Bro, this time I could have slept.
If this is not going to work.
I should then
bring him at night.
I'll just stream at night.
Why dogs? Come on, bro.
Why you do this to me?
>> [laughter]
>> I'm playing
I'm getting I can't
been waiting. [singing]
Waiting
all night. I have
I have
work
in 3 hours.
Let me play.
>> Your feelings.
Well,
I went for hours.
I had tweeted.
Focus using the
first out of the signal nobody ever ever
likes. You maximize the frame rate and
enemy visibility. I know your tricks, so
it's not going to work on me this time.
>> [laughter]
>> I miss good driver uh
three.
Wait, you can pick up arrows, okay.
Best game ever.
I didn't know.
First time actually using the bow in
this game, though.
>> Oh, what is this a glitch?
I told you I played the game. I was
using AK and grinding AK. All those
stuff.
Other guns, I didn't grind the
bow yet.
I can you place it in the ground? Oh,
you can.
Yeah, this other I'm left clicking.
What am I doing?
>> [laughter]
>> How about to shoot yourself in the knee?
Leave the tree alone for the love of
Jesus.
Oh, confirm.
I'm so hungry, Mr. Tree.
I get I get 10 more 10 more arrows.
Okay, 10 more arrows.
Let me finish this. Oh, there's a gap
over here.
I get four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Final one, we can just send it up to the
sky.
Imagine if it hits me.
That would be so uncool.
Did it not fell down?
Did I send that arrow to space?
I think I did.
Okay, we'll collect the arrows back.
Sorry for hurting you, Mr. Tree.
Wait a minute.
I unleashed around 80 or 50 on this
tree. I only got 27 back. What?
This tree ate my arrows. What?
What?
How could you eat my arrows?
Okay, that was a good discovery.
Hey, did you eat bullets as well?
Yeah, you don't. Okay.
Wait, I can't I can reload my arrows.
Oh, well, never mind. S26, okay.
Mhm.
I didn't say anything.
>> [clears throat]
>> Okay, let me see.
Mhm.
What an embarrassment of a launch for
bulkhead. It's okay.
Because streamers get to play this game
while other stuff are sitting in a queue
of failure to link the game or get
banned once we join servers.
Do you close to up there's the one and
job? Look.
Uh if it doesn't work now, I I just want
to go sleep.
I'll just do the stream tomorrow. I
mean, tonight tonight.
I'll just check it one last time.
Punch Christopher in the tutorial.
>> Man, come on.
I want to join.
But some people are
smashing this server updating it.
Okay, I'm a spamming it. I'm spamming
it. I'm spamming it.
Wild Cat, come on. Get your stuff
together.
People are saying Wild Card's getting
the details because of someone and now
Battle for six is pretty funny.
>> [laughter]
>> Wait, Battle for six is
having 50% off? Wait, what?
Wait, no way.
Wait, actually?
What the [\h__\h]
Wait, if Battle for six is 50% off, then
I should buy that.
Bro, it's 50% off.
No way.
It's 50% off.
No way it is 50% off.
Bro, okay, I'm buying it.
I don't have money though.
Help.
>> [laughter]
>> Why?
Why dogs?
Why do dogs so
Wait, can I join Born Peanuts server or
something?
Where does he
Wait.
How are these streamers able to play,
man?
I mean, I did something and I lost
everything. Oh, [\h__\h]
Okay, I lost the server browser. I lost
the server browser. Oh my god.
Are you kidding me?
Oh my god.
Haha, what to do?
I want to go sleep.
I want to go sleep, people.
I got like noodles.
Up noodle.
I want to go sleep. The weather is so
cold today and
It's
like having a a It's like turning on AC
and sleeping at night moment.
I want to go sleep. If this is not
working, I want to go sleep.
Okay, I'll get the
I'll go get the achievement. I'm going
to go punch Christopher in this face.
Cuz I can do that.
I'm going to punch him.
Wait, Christopher would be the guy with
a grenade and everything, right now
firing.
I got practice place
area.
>> Favorite customer.
>> [clears throat]
>> That's the wild dogs.
Where is the game?
I'm winning a match without
another thing is calling a point.
>> What are you after?
>> Is there any weapons?
M4
60 round bag
crazy man
But then this feels like Call of Duty.
Nice.
>> I would
uh
That's so far away.
Ooh, headshot.
This is hard.
Could I get by you?
I I I love that many people are just
buying
Battlefield 6 and playing it right now
cuz it's 50% off.
That's crazy.
>> Hey, someone got back.
Is it actually out?
Uh, bruh.
#wilddogscome on give me something.
>> Okay, I'm quitting it.
The thing is not
I
I don't know what to say.
Everyone will be logged out, okay?
I think you were right, Cali. So, I
don't know if you're still here, but
I should have just slept.
>> [laughter]
>> Why am I commenting to this?
I was like, you know, I was like, I'm
going to make at least 100k
today.
And make enough money to unlock the AK
like AK-47.
and stuff.
That was my plan.
I had so much plans.
I was like, "I'm going to do this. I'm
going to do that. I'm going to do that.
This and that. Blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah."
And the end, I'm stuck here
in the void.
Will that guy even play?
Let me get some water.
Okay, there there
Should I go sleep?
Do she all
Do she all do she all do she all Should
I just go sleep? What I don't I don't
Uh
Now the thing is not everyone.
Sometimes I would need to understand
that I shouldn't always depend on a game
just to do a stream. Sometimes I don't
know why.
I feel like lately not
Uh I've been only doing game streams.
I've not been doing much.
And that's
That's bad that you I am supposed to
entertain.
Oh wait, I got it.
Server though cool.
Huh
Bro
bro
>> [laughter]
>> Uh crazy.
I had that.
We have armor is also 75% off.
>> Haha.
Or she all
Guys, it's 4:30. Should I just go sleep?
We've been waiting for how long? 3
hours? 2 hours?
How do you unlock the bow?
Level 17. Okay, recon.
Okay, I need to play the sniper more.
>> Next thing is
go to the
Level 60 for level three armor?
What the hell?
Level 100 for level four armor?
No way.
They're literally level maxing
everything.
>> Battle's pitched 33. Your A match The
hot zone is a roaming XP in War Dogs is
>> a tutorial.
I'll just do the tutorial and start
punching the thingy just for the
just for the achievement.
>> I would yeah, I just need a bunch of
Mhm.
Oh, hello. Welcome.
Hello,
top top rag channel. Welcome.
How's the game? Uh
or
How are you? I'm doing great. How are
you?
Oh my god, the game is lagging. Oh, my
PC is lagging.
Can call me soil? What?
It's It's It's fine. It's fine. I'll
call you by your name.
Enter the warehouse. Do so. this side.
Also, where is this?
Ah, this side.
>> Ah.
Okay.
Welcome to the training center.
I take it you've already heard about our
little video.
Good.
Turn on the projector
and scroll
and press play
to start watching.
>> Uh.
Please call me sir. Okay.
I'll call you sir then. Fine.
>> Hey, genuinely thank you for purchasing
our game and joining us on this journey.
War Dogs is an early access title and as
such all progression
>> Why is it lagging?
>> powers and cosmetics will be reset
seasonally. We are currently working
towards building our full vision of War
Dogs with more content, expanded meta
game, and permanent progression systems.
And we'll be releasing on multiple
platforms. But until then, we hope you
make money, lose money, and love every
second of winning it back.
Now that that's finally over, you can
head across the hall and start your
>> Okay, everything is low.
>> That fine man is an equipment vendor.
You'll find these guys standing next to
weapons posters across Back Alley.
>> I have to get to the next room, then
I'll get the
>> Get some ammo from him.
Let's get started.
>> Oh, boy.
>> I know you've done this before, but I
need to see it for myself, so
when you're ready, fire at
With the right equipment,
bullets can easily penetrate weaker
materials, like glass, wood, and cloth,
obviously.
Hit the target through the wood.
See for yourself.
Solid work.
Unlike wood,
>> One more, one more.
>> it's impenetrable, causing bullets to
ricochet.
Fire at the edge of the container and
watch THE BULLET RICOCHET.
GOOD JOB.
>> UH
>> LET'S SEE WHAT YOU'RE LIKE WITH
EXPLOSIVES.
Go to the vendor and get some grenades.
>> Please don't misunderstand me. I'm not
one of the words, okay?
Uh I don't know what to draw, so can I
draw you as a fan art? Uh feel free to.
It's fine.
>> Go and grab a grenade from the vendor
now.
Now, TAKE A GRENADE
FROM THE SLOT FOUR OF YOUR attack vest
and throw it through the top window.
GOOD WORK.
NOW, GO BACK TO
>> HEY, IS IT OKAY FOR THEM to have
the red blood splashes?
Cuz
if I'm up up if I'm doing this game
putting playing this game on uploading
the vod which stream what to Bilibili,
China won't like this.
They don't like the red thingy.
Violence.
If you have a Insta
Uh I have an Instagram account that is
at the joke next or you can just
or just you can post it with the hashtag
joke list.
On Twitter just find it on my Twitter
or YouTube channel it has it.
Of course.
This guy.
Yeah, let's get that achievement. That's
why we're here.
Great stuff for
It is.
>> [panting]
>> I got to go to buy that.
I'll be ready in 3 hours. What why is
there like a time limit?
Was there like a time limit?
Yes, I got the I got the
I got the
actually got the
achievement. Let's go.
You might
The value might as well as still retain
my achievement. Yes, I do.
80% of the people have that achievement.
Why?
Crazy there.
Bye, yeah, guys. I'm thinking if I I
should just Not too bad. It's going to
be fine. I have to wake up in 2 hours.
Bye.
I wish you
>> It is Spain.
Uh
The launch issues are
Oh, he made a video.
Huh.
Joe Brummer gave me an update about
what's happening in with the
If they can compensate, but
Their anti-cheat is going crazy.
Ah! I shouldn't have streamed, bro, if
this game was having issues.
But, again,
you have to understand, it's a small
studios playing their best.
And even triple-A games have [\h__\h] show
and they're
>> [laughter]
>> in their launch days.
So, it is fine.
So, you know what?
For now,
Minna,
I'll just quit the game.
I'll wrap up the stream here.
Even though there's not much going on.
We play and we
blew the helicopter for a bit and crash
landed it. That's about it.
Other than that, it was a fun.
Yeah.
So, yeah.
Since the game is not able to be it's
having issues and everything,
we'll wrapping it up here. It was really
fun to at least play the firing range
stuff, etc.
and everything. And also get that
achievement of punching Christopher.
I should have done that in the I did
that in the beta, but I forgot to do it
in the
this thing. [music] I mean, when the
alpha I mean, early access released
today. But, yeah.
Uh
I will be streaming the game later
tonight.
Uh
like my at night or something.
So, yeah.
Uh that's about it, Minna. Thank you
again for today.
Have a good one.
I'll
What do you call it?
I'll have to go
and sleep for I'd like take a small nap
for like a 1 hour and just
get back up.
But yeah, thank you again everyone for
coming by today.
Those who came by today are
Let me read out your names. Alicia
Thank you for coming by. Cali Thank you
for coming by.
Uh it's Aaron. It's Aaron. Thank you for
coming by.
Then on Kick we got the product John
Soil son
for coming Thank you for coming by as
well.
And all the lurkers who are lurking on
YouTube, Twitch, Kick, and Rumble, and
Twitter
or X. Thank you for lurking. Thank you
for watching the stream.
Uh if you're watching it from
as of all later. Thank you to those who
are
um
Thank you to those who are also um What
do you call it? Thank you to those who
are also
uh watching this stream vod from Billy
Billy.
Thank you for
um Thank you for
coming.
>> [music]
>> and uh watching that.
Wait.
Uh
I think with that I'll wrap it up.
What's
uh Bye-bye.
>> I